[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Is this just another illustration as this case has already illuminated of social media completely out of control with a certain element of teenagers in America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Absolutely, completely out of control.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "These are the threats from the two teenage girls you have in custody now, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "That's correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "VBZ", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 59, "question": "What did they say that made you arrest them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, one says, \"You ripped my family apart, you made my cousin cry so when I see you, (EXPLETIVE DELETED), it's going to be a homicide.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane Doe"]}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", ",", "``", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 63, "question": "And the next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "And the next is, \"I'll celebrate by beating the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) out of Jane Doe.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Did you feel that was a significant thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "It was -- it was a very emotionally packed moment that occurred in that courtroom where watching this young boy suffer once he realized what the punishment and what had happened at that point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Does she feel any sense of forgiveness to these two young men that did this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Well, she has not at this point forgiven anybody for what she's been through, the terrible ordeal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Can you repeat that question, please, sir?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I'm really asking how you're feeling today as the father of a young man who has been convicted of raping a young teenaged girl.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Do you feel a sense of guilt, Mr. Richmond, about the fact you were not there for your son as a father for more than a very little period in his life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Of course I feel a sense of guilt.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Richmond"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "You must feel a sense of shame, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, first of all, they had no text messages for Ma'lik.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "But I also understand your son has been convicted of a very serious offense in raping a young woman and what I want to ask you is what is your feeling towards that young girl who went through this terrible ordeal and what is your feeling towards her family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, I feel sorry for the young girl.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Did you not think that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, you have about five different questions there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Would you have advised your client to apologize for a crime he's always denied committing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, his apology was for the pain that he caused.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Will you be appealing then, in that case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "There will be an appeal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Can you stay for another segment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What does it say about Steubenville or indeed, America and teenagers today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, the judge did find that both defendants were delinquent, in other words, that they were guilty of the crime of rape.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Steubenville", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "How do we advance this to a higher level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "TO", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I think you have to start from a position that the biggest victim here is not your client.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "-- what is your view of that behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Oh, it's abhorrent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Ma'lik Richmond had one text out of a day full of testimony full of text messages and e-mails and tweets which he had none, okay?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "But it's not really just about the text.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Richmond"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "How do we -- where do we go from here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Where we go from here is we say we acknowledge if a person does something wrong, then we make amends to that person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Oh, so you're not going to appeal from the judgment of delinquency?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I don't believe -- I don't believe he should have to register as a sex offender until he dies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Either way, would you want to be judged for the rest of your life for something you did at 16?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Well then maybe you ought to think about that -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Excuse me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Wait, wait, wait.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Did you choose to make adult films?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I was a young girl.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Did you choose to make adult films and profit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "ORDS: I was a 15-year-old girl, and I don't need to apologize to you, honey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "What is the relevance of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Well, she's saying don't judge someone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "I'm not -- did you hear me disagree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "OK, I've got to leave it there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "What did you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "You know, Piers, it's not shocking to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Are these just very unusual children that get affected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I'm glad you asked that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I think with this young man, you had an unbelievable recipe for disaster on so many different fronts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "But where was she with this seven foot spreadsheet of murderers, with taking him to these gun ranges all the time, feeding this tormented, weird obsessive loner mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "It enrages me, to tell you the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Is she just a cold-blooded psycho killer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "I would not like to see her out in society, if you want to know my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Very quickly, on that, of course the great debate is can somebody who is having these outrageous fantasies, really evil stuff, does that make them a criminal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "MD", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Well, you know, it all begins with fantasy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "But what did you make of her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I'm delighted she's done it, for whatever her reason.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "And why don't you just talk me through what you believe caused the tragic death of this young girl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Just from that point of view, has she been suffering since the death of Cous-Cous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Yeah, she's been under a lot of stress.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130318pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Would you say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Well, I think this gives just a powerful example of really how powerful these creatures are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]